{
    "N3D1KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "駐車", "answer": "ちゅうしゃ", "english_answer": "park" },
        { "question": "駐車場", "answer": "ちゅうしゃじょう", "english_answer": "parking lot" },
        { "question": "無休", "answer": "むきゅう", "english_answer": "work without holiday" },
        { "question": "無料", "answer": "むりょう", "english_answer": "free of charge" },
        { "question": "無理", "answer": "むり", "english_answer": "unreasonable, impossible" },
        { "question": "無い", "answer": "ない", "english_answer": "doesn't exist, don't have" },
        { "question": "満車", "answer": "まんしゃ", "english_answer": "full of cars" },
        { "question": "満員", "answer": "まんいん", "english_answer": "full of people" },
        { "question": "不満", "answer": "ふまん", "english_answer": "dissatisfied" },
        { "question": "方向", "answer": "ほうこう", "english_answer": "direction" },
        { "question": "向こう", "answer": "むこう", "english_answer": "over there" },
        { "question": "向かう", "answer": "むかう", "english_answer": "go forward" },
        { "question": "～向き", "answer": "～むき", "english_answer": "be suitable for ~" },
        { "question": "禁止", "answer": "きんし", "english_answer": "prohibition" },
        { "question": "関心", "answer": "かんしん", "english_answer": "interest" },
        { "question": "関する", "answer": "かんする", "english_answer": "related" },
        { "question": "関係", "answer": "かんけい", "english_answer": "relation, connection" },
        { "question": "係", "answer": "かかり", "english_answer": "person in charge" },
        { "question": "無断", "answer": "むだん", "english_answer": "without permission" },
        { "question": "断水", "answer": "だんすい", "english_answer": "suspension of water supply" },
        { "question": "断る", "answer": "ことわる", "english_answer": "refuse" }
    ],
    "N3D2KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "横断", "answer": "おうだん", "english_answer": "crossing" },
        { "question": "横断歩道", "answer": "おうだんほどう", "english_answer": "pedestrian crossing" },
        { "question": "横", "answer": "よこ", "english_answer": "side" },
        { "question": "押す", "answer": "おす", "english_answer": "push" },
        { "question": "押さえる", "answer": "おさえる", "english_answer": "hold down" },
        { "question": "押し入れ", "answer": "おしいれ", "english_answer": "closet" },
        { "question": "押しボタン式", "answer": "おしぼたんしき", "english_answer": "push button" },
        { "question": "入学式", "answer": "にゅうがくしき", "english_answer": "school entrance ceremony" },
        { "question": "数式", "answer": "すうしき", "english_answer": "numerical formula" },
        { "question": "送信", "answer": "そうしん", "english_answer": "transmit" },
        { "question": "信じる", "answer": "しんじる", "english_answer": "believe" },
        { "question": "自信", "answer": "じしん", "english_answer": "confidence" },
        { "question": "信用", "answer": "しんよう", "english_answer": "trust" },
        { "question": "信号", "answer": "しんごう", "english_answer": "signal, traffic light" },
        { "question": "～号車", "answer": "～ごうしゃ", "english_answer": "carriage number ~" },
        { "question": "正確", "answer": "せいかく", "english_answer": "correct, accurate" },
        { "question": "確かめる", "answer": "たしかめる", "english_answer": "confirm, verify" },
        { "question": "確か", "answer": "たしか", "english_answer": "certain" },
        { "question": "確認", "answer": "かくにん", "english_answer": "confirmation" },
        { "question": "認める", "answer": "みとめる", "english_answer": "admit, approve" },
        { "question": "飛行場", "answer": "ひこうじょう", "english_answer": "airport" },
        { "question": "飛ぶ", "answer": "とぶ", "english_answer": "fly" }
    ],
    "N3D3KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "", "answer": "", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "非常に", "answer": "ひじょうに", "english_answer": "extremely" },
        { "question": "非常口", "answer": "ひじょうぐち", "english_answer": "emergency exit" },
        { "question": "日常", "answer": "にちじょう", "english_answer": "usual, everyday" },
        { "question": "正常", "answer": "せいじょう", "english_answer": "normal" },
        { "question": "～階", "answer": "かい", "english_answer": "floor" },
        { "question": "階段", "answer": "かいだん", "english_answer": "stairs" },
        { "question": "箱", "answer": "はこ", "english_answer": "box" },
        { "question": "ごみ箱", "answer": "ごみばこ", "english_answer": "trash box" },
        { "question": "危険", "answer": "きけん", "english_answer": "danger" },
        { "question": "危ない", "answer": "あぶない", "english_answer": "dangerous" },
        { "question": "捨てる", "answer": "すてる", "english_answer": "throw away" }
    ],
    "N3D4KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "線", "answer": "せん", "english_answer": "line" },
        { "question": "～番線", "answer": "ばんせん", "english_answer": "platform number ~" },
        { "question": "全面", "answer": "ぜんめん", "english_answer": "whole" },
        { "question": "画面", "answer": "がめん", "english_answer": "screen" },
        { "question": "～方面", "answer": "ほうめん", "english_answer": "~ area" },
        { "question": "普通", "answer": "ふつう", "english_answer": "ordinary" },
        { "question": "各駅", "answer": "かくえき", "english_answer": "every station" },
        { "question": "各国", "answer": "かっこく", "english_answer": "every country" },
        { "question": "各自", "answer": "かくじ", "english_answer": "respective/each person" },
        { "question": "目次", "answer": "もくじ", "english_answer": "contents" },
        { "question": "次回", "answer": "じかい", "english_answer": "next time" },
        { "question": "次", "answer": "つぎ", "english_answer": "next" },
        { "question": "快速", "answer": "かいそく", "english_answer": "rapid" },
        { "question": "高速道路", "answer": "こうそくどうろ", "english_answer": "highway" },
        { "question": "速度", "answer": "そくど", "english_answer": "speed" },
        { "question": "速い", "answer": "はやい", "english_answer": "fast" },
        { "question": "通過", "answer": "つうか", "english_answer": "passage, transit" },
        { "question": "過去", "answer": "かこ", "english_answer": "past" },
        { "question": "過ぎる", "answer": "すぎる", "english_answer": "pass" },
        { "question": "地下鉄", "answer": "ちかてつ", "english_answer": "subway" },
        { "question": "鉄道", "answer": "てつどう", "english_answer": "railway" },
        { "question": "鉄", "answer": "てつ", "english_answer": "steel" }
    ],
    "N3D5KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "指定", "answer": "してい", "english_answer": "specify, designate" },
        { "question": "指定席", "answer": "していせき", "english_answer": "reserved seat" },
        { "question": "指", "answer": "ゆび", "english_answer": "finger" },
        { "question": "指輪", "answer": "ゆびわ", "english_answer": "ring" },
        { "question": "定休日", "answer": "ていきゅうび", "english_answer": "set/regular holiday" },
        { "question": "安定", "answer": "あんてい", "english_answer": "stable" },
        { "question": "席", "answer": "せき", "english_answer": "seat" },
        { "question": "出席", "answer": "しゅっせき", "english_answer": "attend" },
        { "question": "欠席", "answer": "けっせき", "english_answer": "absence" },
        { "question": "自由", "answer": "じゆう", "english_answer": "free" },
        { "question": "自由席", "answer": "じゆうせき", "english_answer": "non-reserved seat" },
        { "question": "理由", "answer": "りゆう", "english_answer": "reason" },
        { "question": "番号", "answer": "ばんごう", "english_answer": "number" },
        { "question": "～番線", "answer": "ばんせん", "english_answer": "platform number ~" },
        { "question": "～番", "answer": "ばん", "english_answer": "number ~" },
        { "question": "窓", "answer": "まど", "english_answer": "window" },
        { "question": "窓口", "answer": "まどぐち", "english_answer": "teller's window" },
        { "question": "両側", "answer": "りょうがわ", "english_answer": "both sides" },
        { "question": "窓側", "answer": "まどがわ", "english_answer": "window seat" },
        { "question": "右側", "answer": "みぎがわ", "english_answer": "right side" },
        { "question": "通路", "answer": "つうろ", "english_answer": "aisle" },
        { "question": "道路", "answer": "どうろ", "english_answer": "road" },
        { "question": "線路", "answer": "せんろ", "english_answer": "railway" }
    ],
    "N3D6KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "停車", "answer": "ていしゃ", "english_answer": "stop a vehicle" },
        { "question": "バス停", "answer": "バスてい", "english_answer": "bus stop" },
        { "question": "整理", "answer": "せいり", "english_answer": "tidy" },
        { "question": "整理券", "answer": "せいりけん", "english_answer": "numbered ticket" },
        { "question": "駐車券", "answer": "ちゅうしゃけん", "english_answer": "parking ticket" },
        { "question": "乗車券", "answer": "じょうしゃけん", "english_answer": "boarding ticket" },
        { "question": "回数券", "answer": "かいすうけん", "english_answer": "book of commuter tickets" },
        { "question": "現金", "answer": "げんきん", "english_answer": "cash" },
        { "question": "表現", "answer": "ひょうげん", "english_answer": "expression" },
        { "question": "現れる", "answer": "あらわれる", "english_answer": "appear" },
        { "question": "両親", "answer": "りょうしん", "english_answer": "parents" },
        { "question": "～両", "answer": "りょう", "english_answer": "~ cars on train" },
        { "question": "取り替える", "answer": "とりかえる", "english_answer": "exchange" },
        { "question": "両替", "answer": "りょうがえ", "english_answer": "exchange" },
        { "question": "着替える", "answer": "きがえる", "english_answer": "change clothes" },
        { "question": "優先席", "answer": "ゆうせんせき", "english_answer": "priority seat" },
        { "question": "女優", "answer": "じょゆう", "english_answer": "actress" },
        { "question": "優しい", "answer": "やさしい", "english_answer": "kind" },
        { "question": "座席", "answer": "ざせき", "english_answer": "seat" },
        { "question": "正座", "answer": "せいざ", "english_answer": "Japanese style sit" },
        { "question": "座る", "answer": "すわる", "english_answer": "sit" },
        { "question": "降車口", "answer": "こうしゃぐち", "english_answer": "exit for getting off" },
        { "question": "以降", "answer": "いこう", "english_answer": "after ~" },
        { "question": "降りる", "answer": "おりる", "english_answer": "get off" },
        { "question": "降る", "answer": "ふる", "english_answer": "fall" }
    ],
    "N3D7KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "未定", "answer": "みてい", "english_answer": "undecided, indefinite" },
        { "question": "～未満", "answer": "みまん", "english_answer": "less than" },
        { "question": "未来", "answer": "みらい", "english_answer": "future" },
        { "question": "週末", "answer": "しゅうまつ", "english_answer": "weekend" },
        { "question": "年末", "answer": "ねんまつ", "english_answer": "end of the year" },
        { "question": "月末", "answer": "げつまつ", "english_answer": "end of the month" },
        { "question": "若い", "answer": "わかい", "english_answer": "young" },
        { "question": "晩", "answer": "ばん", "english_answer": "night" },
        { "question": "晩ご飯", "answer": "ばんごはん", "english_answer": "dinner" },
        { "question": "今晩", "answer": "こんばん", "english_answer": "tonight" },
        { "question": "毎晩", "answer": "まいばん", "english_answer": "every night" },
        { "question": "～島", "answer": "とう", "english_answer": "~ Island" },
        { "question": "島", "answer": "しま", "english_answer": "island" },
        { "question": "皿", "answer": "さら", "english_answer": "plate" },
        { "question": "灰皿", "answer": "はいざら", "english_answer": "ashtray" },
        { "question": "出血", "answer": "しゅっけつ", "english_answer": "bleed" },
        { "question": "血", "answer": "ち", "english_answer": "blood" },
        { "question": "救助", "answer": "きゅうじょ", "english_answer": "rescue, help" },
        { "question": "助ける", "answer": "たすける", "english_answer": "help" }
    ],
    "N3D8KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "準備", "answer": "じゅんび", "english_answer": "preparation" },
        { "question": "備える", "answer": "そなえる", "english_answer": "prepare" },
        { "question": "営業", "answer": "えいぎょう", "english_answer": "business" },
        { "question": "開閉", "answer": "かいへい", "english_answer": "open and shut" },
        { "question": "閉まる", "answer": "しまる", "english_answer": "shut/close" },
        { "question": "閉める", "answer": "しめる", "english_answer": "shut/close" },
        { "question": "案内", "answer": "あんない", "english_answer": "information" },
        { "question": "案", "answer": "あん", "english_answer": "a suggestion, proposal, plan" },
        { "question": "家内", "answer": "かない", "english_answer": "wife" },
        { "question": "内側", "answer": "うちがわ", "english_answer": "inside" },
        { "question": "以内", "answer": "いない", "english_answer": "within" },
        { "question": "国内", "answer": "こくない", "english_answer": "domestic" },
        { "question": "予定", "answer": "よてい", "english_answer": "a plan/schedule" },
        { "question": "予習", "answer": "よしゅう", "english_answer": "preparation (pre-study)" },
        { "question": "予約", "answer": "よやく", "english_answer": "an appointment/reservation" },
        { "question": "約～", "answer": "やく", "english_answer": "approximately" }
    ],
    "N3D9KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "禁煙", "answer": "きんえん", "english_answer": "no smoking" },
        { "question": "煙", "answer": "けむり", "english_answer": "smoke" },
        { "question": "本当", "answer": "ほんとう", "english_answer": "the truth" },
        { "question": "当たる", "answer": "あたる", "english_answer": "hit/win" },
        { "question": "当～", "answer": "とう", "english_answer": "this" },
        { "question": "当たり前", "answer": "あたりまえ", "english_answer": "natural, not surprising" },
        { "question": "全部", "answer": "ぜんぶ", "english_answer": "all/whole" },
        { "question": "全席", "answer": "ぜんせき", "english_answer": "all seats" },
        { "question": "安全", "answer": "あんぜん", "english_answer": "safe" },
        { "question": "客", "answer": "きゃく", "english_answer": "a customer" },
        { "question": "お客様", "answer": "おきゃくさま", "english_answer": "a customer" },
        { "question": "様子", "answer": "ようす", "english_answer": "appearance/situation" },
        { "question": "～様", "answer": "さま", "english_answer": "an honorific added to people's names, particularly in letters" },
        { "question": "理解", "answer": "りかい", "english_answer": "understand" },
        { "question": "解説", "answer": "かいせつ", "english_answer": "an explanation" },
        { "question": "解答", "answer": "かいとう", "english_answer": "an answer" },
        { "question": "分解", "answer": "ぶんかい", "english_answer": "take apart" },
        { "question": "協力", "answer": "きょうりょく", "english_answer": "cooperation" },
        { "question": "願う", "answer": "ねがう", "english_answer": "wish" }
    ],
    "N3D10KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "観光", "answer": "かんこう", "english_answer": "sightseeing" },
        { "question": "観客", "answer": "かんきゃく", "english_answer": "spectator, audience" },
        { "question": "動物園", "answer": "どうぶつえん", "english_answer": "a zoo" },
        { "question": "空港", "answer": "くうこう", "english_answer": "an airport" },
        { "question": "港", "answer": "みなと", "english_answer": "a port" },
        { "question": "～港", "answer": "こう", "english_answer": "port" },
        { "question": "遊園地", "answer": "ゆうえんち", "english_answer": "an amusement park" },
        { "question": "遊ぶ", "answer": "あそぶ", "english_answer": "play" },
        { "question": "美術館", "answer": "びじゅつかん", "english_answer": "a museum" },
        { "question": "美しい", "answer": "うつくしい", "english_answer": "beautiful" },
        { "question": "美人", "answer": "びじん", "english_answer": "a beautiful woman" },
        { "question": "美術", "answer": "びじゅつ", "english_answer": "(fine) art" },
        { "question": "手術", "answer": "しゅじゅつ", "english_answer": "surgery, operation" },
        { "question": "技術", "answer": "ぎじゅつ", "english_answer": "technique, technology" },
        { "question": "神社", "answer": "じんじゃ", "english_answer": "a shrine" },
        { "question": "神様", "answer": "かみさま", "english_answer": "a god" },
        { "question": "神経質", "answer": "しんけいしつ", "english_answer": "nervous" },
        { "question": "～寺", "answer": "じ", "english_answer": "temple" },
        { "question": "お寺", "answer": "おてら", "english_answer": "a temple" }
    ],
    "N3D11KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "市役所", "answer": "しやくしょ", "english_answer": "the city office" },
        { "question": "役員", "answer": "やくいん", "english_answer": "an officer/member" },
        { "question": "役に立つ", "answer": "やくにたつ", "english_answer": "useful" },
        { "question": "郵便", "answer": "ゆうびん", "english_answer": "mail" },
        { "question": "郵便局", "answer": "ゆうびんきょく", "english_answer": "a post office" },
        { "question": "薬局", "answer": "やっきょく", "english_answer": "a drug store" },
        { "question": "交番", "answer": "こうばん", "english_answer": "a police box" },
        { "question": "交換", "answer": "こうかん", "english_answer": "exchange" },
        { "question": "交通", "answer": "こうつう", "english_answer": "transport" },
        { "question": "差", "answer": "さ", "english_answer": "difference" },
        { "question": "差し出す", "answer": "さしだす", "english_answer": "hand in" },
        { "question": "差出人", "answer": "さしだしにん", "english_answer": "a sender" },
        { "question": "交差点", "answer": "こうさてん", "english_answer": "an intersection" },
        { "question": "～点", "answer": "てん", "english_answer": "points" },
        { "question": "点数", "answer": "てんすう", "english_answer": "score/points" },
        { "question": "歩道橋", "answer": "ほどうきょう", "english_answer": "a foot bridge" },
        { "question": "橋", "answer": "はし", "english_answer": "a bridge" },
        { "question": "公園", "answer": "こうえん", "english_answer": "a park" }
    ],
    "N3D12KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "受信", "answer": "じゅしん", "english_answer": "receive" },
        { "question": "受ける", "answer": "うける", "english_answer": "receive" },
        { "question": "受験", "answer": "じゅけん", "english_answer": "an entrance examination" },
        { "question": "付ける", "answer": "つける", "english_answer": "put on" },
        { "question": "受付", "answer": "うけつけ", "english_answer": "a reception" },
        { "question": "片付ける", "answer": "かたづける", "english_answer": "tidy up" },
        { "question": "付く", "answer": "つく", "english_answer": "stick to" },
        { "question": "科学", "answer": "かがく", "english_answer": "science" },
        { "question": "内科", "answer": "ないか", "english_answer": "internal medicine" },
        { "question": "外科", "answer": "げか", "english_answer": "surgery department" },
        { "question": "教科書", "answer": "きょうかしょ", "english_answer": "a textbook" },
        { "question": "耳鼻科", "answer": "じびか", "english_answer": "ears and nose department" },
        { "question": "鼻", "answer": "はな", "english_answer": "a nose" },
        { "question": "婦人", "answer": "ふじん", "english_answer": "a woman" },
        { "question": "主婦", "answer": "しゅふ", "english_answer": "a housewife" },
        { "question": "産婦人科", "answer": "さんふじんか", "english_answer": "obstetrics and gynecology" },
        { "question": "形式", "answer": "けいしき", "english_answer": "form/type" },
        { "question": "整形外科", "answer": "せいけいげか", "english_answer": "orthopedics department" },
        { "question": "人形", "answer": "にんぎょう", "english_answer": "a doll/puppet" },
        { "question": "図形", "answer": "ずけい", "english_answer": "a diagram" },
        { "question": "形", "answer": "かたち", "english_answer": "shape/form" },
        { "question": "骨折", "answer": "こっせつ", "english_answer": "a bone fracture" },
        { "question": "骨", "answer": "ほね", "english_answer": "a bone" },
        { "question": "右折", "answer": "うせつ", "english_answer": "a right turn" },
        { "question": "折る", "answer": "おる", "english_answer": "break/fold (something)" },
        { "question": "折れる", "answer": "おれる", "english_answer": "break" },
        { "question": "左折", "answer": "させつ", "english_answer": "a left turn" },
        { "question": "折り紙", "answer": "おりがみ", "english_answer": "Japanese art of folding paper" }
    ],
    "N3D13KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "困る", "answer": "こまる", "english_answer": "be in trouble" },
        { "question": "消防", "answer": "しょうぼう", "english_answer": "fire fighting" },
        { "question": "消す", "answer": "けす", "english_answer": "extinguish" },
        { "question": "消える", "answer": "きえる", "english_answer": "be extinguished, disappear" },
        { "question": "消しゴム", "answer": "けしゴム", "english_answer": "an eraser" },
        { "question": "予防", "answer": "よぼう", "english_answer": "precaution, prevention" },
        { "question": "防ぐ", "answer": "ふせぐ", "english_answer": "prevent" },
        { "question": "救急車", "answer": "きゅうきゅうしゃ", "english_answer": "an ambulance" },
        { "question": "救う", "answer": "すくう", "english_answer": "save" },
        { "question": "警官", "answer": "けいかん", "english_answer": "a police officer" },
        { "question": "警察", "answer": "けいさつ", "english_answer": "police" },
        { "question": "警察署", "answer": "けいさつしょ", "english_answer": "a police station" },
        { "question": "事故", "answer": "じこ", "english_answer": "an accident" },
        { "question": "故～", "answer": "こ", "english_answer": "the late Mr." },
        { "question": "故障", "answer": "こしょう", "english_answer": "break-down, failure" },
        { "question": "伝言", "answer": "でんごん", "english_answer": "a message" },
        { "question": "伝える", "answer": "つたえる", "english_answer": "convey/communicate" },
        { "question": "手伝う", "answer": "てつだう", "english_answer": "help" }
    ],
    "N3D14KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "黄色", "answer": "きいろ", "english_answer": "yellow" },
        { "question": "黄色い", "answer": "きいろい", "english_answer": "yellow" },
        { "question": "絵画", "answer": "かいが", "english_answer": "a painting" },
        { "question": "絵", "answer": "え", "english_answer": "a picture" },
        { "question": "絵本", "answer": "えほん", "english_answer": "a picture book" },
        { "question": "～組", "answer": "くみ", "english_answer": "pairs" },
        { "question": "組む", "answer": "くむ", "english_answer": "team up" },
        { "question": "番組", "answer": "ばんぐみ", "english_answer": "a (TV) program" },
        { "question": "組み立てる", "answer": "くみたてる", "english_answer": "put together" },
        { "question": "約束", "answer": "やくそく", "english_answer": "a promise/appointment" },
        { "question": "～束", "answer": "たば", "english_answer": "a bundle, a bunch" },
        { "question": "花束", "answer": "はなたば", "english_answer": "bunch of flowers" },
        { "question": "授業", "answer": "じゅぎょう", "english_answer": "a class" },
        { "question": "教授", "answer": "きょうじゅ", "english_answer": "a professor" },
        { "question": "渡る", "answer": "わたる", "english_answer": "thick" },
        { "question": "渡す", "answer": "わたす", "english_answer": "hand over" },
        { "question": "昔", "answer": "むかし", "english_answer": "long ago, past" }
    ],
    "N3D15KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "必要", "answer": "ひつよう", "english_answer": "necessary" },
        { "question": "要る", "answer": "いる", "english_answer": "need" },
        { "question": "重要", "answer": "じゅうよう", "english_answer": "important" },
        { "question": "冷房", "answer": "れいぼう", "english_answer": "air-conditioning" },
        { "question": "冷たい", "answer": "つめたい", "english_answer": "cold" },
        { "question": "冷やす", "answer": "ひやす", "english_answer": "cool" },
        { "question": "冷える", "answer": "ひえる", "english_answer": "become cold" },
        { "question": "冷める", "answer": "さめる", "english_answer": "cool down" },
        { "question": "冷ます", "answer": "さます", "english_answer": "cool something" },
        { "question": "冷蔵庫", "answer": "れいぞうこ", "english_answer": "refrigerator" },
        { "question": "冷凍庫", "answer": "れいとうこ", "english_answer": "freezer" },
        { "question": "凍る", "answer": "こおる", "english_answer": "freeze" },
        { "question": "金庫", "answer": "きんこ", "english_answer": "safe" },
        { "question": "車庫", "answer": "しゃこ", "english_answer": "garage" },
        { "question": "召し上がる", "answer": "めしあがる", "english_answer": "eat (polite form)" },
        { "question": "保存する", "answer": "ほぞんする", "english_answer": "preserve" },
        { "question": "ご存じです", "answer": "ごぞんじです", "english_answer": "know (humble form)" },
        { "question": "存じません", "answer": "ぞんじません", "english_answer": "I don't know" },
        { "question": "必ず", "answer": "かならず", "english_answer": "always, certainly" },
        { "question": "必死", "answer": "ひっし", "english_answer": "desperate" }
    ],
    "N3D16KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "費用", "answer": "ひよう", "english_answer": "expense, cost" },
        { "question": "消費者", "answer": "しょうひしゃ", "english_answer": "consumers" },
        { "question": "旅費", "answer": "りょひ", "english_answer": "travelling expenses" },
        { "question": "会費", "answer": "かいひ", "english_answer": "membership fee" },
        { "question": "期間", "answer": "きかん", "english_answer": "period of time" },
        { "question": "定期券", "answer": "ていきけん", "english_answer": "commuter pass" },
        { "question": "長期", "answer": "ちょうき", "english_answer": "long period" },
        { "question": "短期", "answer": "たんき", "english_answer": "short period" },
        { "question": "期限", "answer": "きげん", "english_answer": "time limit" },
        { "question": "限度", "answer": "げんど", "english_answer": "limit" },
        { "question": "限る", "answer": "かぎる", "english_answer": "limit, restrict" },
        { "question": "限定", "answer": "げんてい", "english_answer": "limitation" },
        { "question": "～製", "answer": "せい", "english_answer": "made in/of ~" },
        { "question": "製品", "answer": "せいひん", "english_answer": "product" },
        { "question": "製造", "answer": "せいぞう", "english_answer": "manufacture" },
        { "question": "造る", "answer": "つくる", "english_answer": "make" },
        { "question": "賞", "answer": "しょう", "english_answer": "prize" },
        { "question": "賞味期限", "answer": "しょうみきげん", "english_answer": "best before" },
        { "question": "賞金", "answer": "しょうきん", "english_answer": "prize money" },
        { "question": "賞品", "answer": "しょうひん", "english_answer": "prize" },
        { "question": "方法", "answer": "ほうほう", "english_answer": "method, way" },
        { "question": "文法", "answer": "ぶんぽう", "english_answer": "grammar" },
        { "question": "温度", "answer": "おんど", "english_answer": "temperature" },
        { "question": "気温", "answer": "きおん", "english_answer": "temperature" },
        { "question": "温かい", "answer": "あたたかい", "english_answer": "warm" },
        { "question": "常温", "answer": "じょうおん", "english_answer": "normal temperature" }
    ],
    "N3D17KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "販売", "answer": "はんばい", "english_answer": "sell" },
        { "question": "自動販売機", "answer": "じどうはんばいき", "english_answer": "vending machine" },
        { "question": "飛行機", "answer": "ひこうき", "english_answer": "airplane" },
        { "question": "機械", "answer": "きかい", "english_answer": "machine" },
        { "question": "機会", "answer": "きかい", "english_answer": "opportunity" },
        { "question": "増加", "answer": "ぞうか", "english_answer": "increase" },
        { "question": "増える", "answer": "ふえる", "english_answer": "increase" },
        { "question": "増やす", "answer": "ふやす", "english_answer": "increase, add" },
        { "question": "減少", "answer": "げんしょう", "english_answer": "decrease" },
        { "question": "減る", "answer": "へる", "english_answer": "decrease, reduce" },
        { "question": "減らす", "answer": "へらす", "english_answer": "decrease" },
        { "question": "量", "answer": "りょう", "english_answer": "quantity" },
        { "question": "数量", "answer": "すうりょう", "english_answer": "amount" },
        { "question": "増量", "answer": "ぞうりょう", "english_answer": "increase the amount" },
        { "question": "減量", "answer": "げんりょう", "english_answer": "loss in quantity" },
        { "question": "氷", "answer": "こおり", "english_answer": "ice" },
        { "question": "返事", "answer": "へんじ", "english_answer": "reply" },
        { "question": "返却", "answer": "へんきゃく", "english_answer": "return" },
        { "question": "返す", "answer": "かえす", "english_answer": "return (something)" },
        { "question": "（お）湯", "answer": "（お）ゆ", "english_answer": "hot water" }
    ],
    "N3D18KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "材料", "answer": "ざいりょう", "english_answer": "ingredients, materials" },
        { "question": "教材", "answer": "きょうざい", "english_answer": "teaching material" },
        { "question": "卵", "answer": "たまご", "english_answer": "egg" },
        { "question": "卵焼き", "answer": "たまごやき", "english_answer": "Japanese omelette" },
        { "question": "牛乳", "answer": "ぎゅうにゅう", "english_answer": "milk" },
        { "question": "粉", "answer": "こな", "english_answer": "powder, flour" },
        { "question": "小麦粉", "answer": "こむぎこ", "english_answer": "wheat flour" },
        { "question": "袋", "answer": "ふくろ", "english_answer": "bag" },
        { "question": "紙袋", "answer": "かみぶくろ", "english_answer": "paper bag" },
        { "question": "ごみ袋", "answer": "ごみぶくろ", "english_answer": "garbage bag" },
        { "question": "手袋", "answer": "てぶくろ", "english_answer": "gloves" },
        { "question": "足袋", "answer": "たび", "english_answer": "tabi (traditional Japanese socks worn with a kimono)" },
        { "question": "混雑", "answer": "こんざつ", "english_answer": "congestion" },
        { "question": "混ぜる", "answer": "まぜる", "english_answer": "be mixed" },
        { "question": "焼く", "answer": "やく", "english_answer": "roast, grill" },
        { "question": "焼ける", "answer": "やける", "english_answer": "be burnt/baked" },
        { "question": "表 (in written documents)", "answer": "ひょう", "english_answer": "table (in written documents)" },
        { "question": "表面", "answer": "ひょうめん", "english_answer": "surface" },
        { "question": "発表", "answer": "はっぴょう", "english_answer": "announcement" },
        { "question": "代表", "answer": "だいひょう", "english_answer": "representative" },
        { "question": "表", "answer": "おもて", "english_answer": "surface, face" },
        { "question": "表す", "answer": "あらわす", "english_answer": "show, express" },
        { "question": "裏", "answer": "うら", "english_answer": "reverse, back" },
        { "question": "裏返す", "answer": "うらかえす", "english_answer": "turnover" }
    ],
    "N3D19KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "留学", "answer": "りゅうがく", "english_answer": "study abroad" },
        { "question": "留守番", "answer": "るすばん", "english_answer": "stay at home" },
        { "question": "保留", "answer": "ほりゅう", "english_answer": "reservation, suspension" },
        { "question": "書留", "answer": "かきとめ", "english_answer": "registration (registered mail)" },
        { "question": "守備", "answer": "しゅび", "english_answer": "defence" },
        { "question": "留守", "answer": "るす", "english_answer": "absence" },
        { "question": "守る", "answer": "まもる", "english_answer": "protect" },
        { "question": "濃い", "answer": "こい", "english_answer": "concentrate, dark (color)" },
        { "question": "薄い", "answer": "うすい", "english_answer": "thin (material), light (color), weak (drink)" },
        { "question": "部分", "answer": "ぶぶん", "english_answer": "part" },
        { "question": "学部", "answer": "がくぶ", "english_answer": "faculty" },
        { "question": "部長", "answer": "ぶちょう", "english_answer": "department head/manager" },
        { "question": "部屋", "answer": "へや", "english_answer": "room" },
        { "question": "数字", "answer": "すうじ", "english_answer": "number" },
        { "question": "数学", "answer": "すうがく", "english_answer": "mathematics" },
        { "question": "数", "answer": "かず", "english_answer": "number" },
        { "question": "数える", "answer": "かぞえる", "english_answer": "count" },
        { "question": "件名", "answer": "けんめい", "english_answer": "subject" },
        { "question": "事件", "answer": "じけん", "english_answer": "incident" },
        { "question": "用件", "answer": "ようけん", "english_answer": "business, matter" },
        { "question": "再入国", "answer": "さいにゅうこく", "english_answer": "re-enter a country" },
        { "question": "再ダイアル", "answer": "さいダイアル", "english_answer": "redial" },
        { "question": "再生", "answer": "さいせい", "english_answer": "regenerate, recycle" },
        { "question": "再来週", "answer": "さらいしゅう", "english_answer": "the week after next" }
    ],
    "N3D20KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "接続", "answer": "せつぞく", "english_answer": "connect" },
        { "question": "面接", "answer": "めんせつ", "english_answer": "interview" },
        { "question": "続く", "answer": "つづく", "english_answer": "continue" },
        { "question": "続ける", "answer": "つづける", "english_answer": "continue" },
        { "question": "表示", "answer": "ひょうじ", "english_answer": "indication, expression" },
        { "question": "指示", "answer": "しじ", "english_answer": "direction, instruction" },
        { "question": "示す", "answer": "しめす", "english_answer": "show, point out" },
        { "question": "戻る", "answer": "もどる", "english_answer": "return" },
        { "question": "戻す", "answer": "もどす", "english_answer": "return, put back" },
        { "question": "完了", "answer": "かんりょう", "english_answer": "completion" },
        { "question": "完全", "answer": "かんぜん", "english_answer": "perfect, complete" },
        { "question": "了解", "answer": "りょうかい", "english_answer": "understand, agree" },
        { "question": "終了", "answer": "しゅうりょう", "english_answer": "end, expiration" },
        { "question": "登録", "answer": "とうろく", "english_answer": "registration" },
        { "question": "登山", "answer": "とざん", "english_answer": "mountain climbing" },
        { "question": "登る", "answer": "のぼる", "english_answer": "climb" },
        { "question": "記録", "answer": "きろく", "english_answer": "record" },
        { "question": "録音", "answer": "ろくおん", "english_answer": "record (sound)" },
        { "question": "録画", "answer": "ろくが", "english_answer": "record (video)" }
    ],
    "N3D21KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "教育", "answer": "きょういく", "english_answer": "education" },
        { "question": "育てる", "answer": "そだてる", "english_answer": "raise, bring up" },
        { "question": "育つ", "answer": "そだつ", "english_answer": "grow" },
        { "question": "種類", "answer": "しゅるい", "english_answer": "type, kind" },
        { "question": "種", "answer": "たね", "english_answer": "seed" },
        { "question": "書類", "answer": "しょるい", "english_answer": "document" },
        { "question": "分類", "answer": "ぶんるい", "english_answer": "classification" },
        { "question": "人類", "answer": "じんるい", "english_answer": "human race" },
        { "question": "教師", "answer": "きょうし", "english_answer": "teacher" },
        { "question": "医師", "answer": "いし", "english_answer": "doctor" },
        { "question": "看護師", "answer": "かんごし", "english_answer": "nurse" },
        { "question": "夫妻", "answer": "ふさい", "english_answer": "husband and wife" },
        { "question": "妻", "answer": "つま", "english_answer": "wife" },
        { "question": "馬", "answer": "うま", "english_answer": "horse" },
        { "question": "乗馬", "answer": "じょうば", "english_answer": "horse riding" },
        { "question": "石けん", "answer": "せっけん", "english_answer": "soap" },
        { "question": "石油", "answer": "せきゆ", "english_answer": "oil (petroleum)" },
        { "question": "石", "answer": "いし", "english_answer": "stone" }
    ],
    "N3D22KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "砂糖", "answer": "さとう", "english_answer": "sugar" },
        { "question": "砂", "answer": "すな", "english_answer": "sand" },
        { "question": "食塩", "answer": "しょくえん", "english_answer": "table salt" },
        { "question": "塩", "answer": "しお", "english_answer": "salt" },
        { "question": "しょう油", "answer": "しょうゆ", "english_answer": "soy sauce" },
        { "question": "灯油", "answer": "とうゆ", "english_answer": "kerosene" },
        { "question": "石油", "answer": "せきゆ", "english_answer": "oil (petroleum)" },
        { "question": "油", "answer": "あぶら", "english_answer": "oil" },
        { "question": "緑茶", "answer": "りょくちゃ", "english_answer": "green tea" },
        { "question": "緑（色）", "answer": "みどりいろ", "english_answer": "green" },
        { "question": "紅茶", "answer": "こうちゃ", "english_answer": "tea" },
        { "question": "口紅", "answer": "くちべに", "english_answer": "lipstick" },
        { "question": "～冊", "answer": "さつ", "english_answer": "counter for books" },
        { "question": "冊数", "answer": "さっすう", "english_answer": "the number of copies" },
        { "question": "～個", "answer": "こ", "english_answer": "counter for general objects" },
        { "question": "個人", "answer": "こじん", "english_answer": "individual person" },
        { "question": "個数", "answer": "こすう", "english_answer": "the number of items" },
        { "question": "団体", "answer": "だんたい", "english_answer": "a group" },
        { "question": "～枚", "answer": "まい", "english_answer": "counter for flat objects" },
        { "question": "枚数", "answer": "まいすう", "english_answer": "the number of sheets/copies" }
    ],
    "N3D23KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "広告", "answer": "こうこく", "english_answer": "advertisement" },
        { "question": "便利", "answer": "べんり", "english_answer": "convenient" },
        { "question": "利用", "answer": "りよう", "english_answer": "use" },
        { "question": "割る", "answer": "わる", "english_answer": "break" },
        { "question": "割れる", "answer": "われる", "english_answer": "crack, cleave" },
        { "question": "割合", "answer": "わりあい", "english_answer": "ratio, percentage" },
        { "question": "割引", "answer": "わりびき", "english_answer": "discount" },
        { "question": "～倍", "answer": "ばい", "english_answer": "times" },
        { "question": "値段", "answer": "ねだん", "english_answer": "price" },
        { "question": "値上げ", "answer": "ねあげ", "english_answer": "price increase" },
        { "question": "値下げ", "answer": "ねさげ", "english_answer": "price reduction" },
        { "question": "商品", "answer": "しょうひん", "english_answer": "goods" },
        { "question": "商店", "answer": "しょうてん", "english_answer": "shop" },
        { "question": "支店", "answer": "してん", "english_answer": "branch" },
        { "question": "支社", "answer": "ししゃ", "english_answer": "branch office" },
        { "question": "本店", "answer": "ほんてん", "english_answer": "main branch of a store" },
        { "question": "本社", "answer": "ほんしゃ", "english_answer": "head office" },
        { "question": "払う", "answer": "はらう", "english_answer": "pay" },
        { "question": "支払い", "answer": "しはらい", "english_answer": "payment" }
    ],
    "N3D24KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "米国", "answer": "べいこく", "english_answer": "United States of America" },
        { "question": "米", "answer": "こめ", "english_answer": "rice" },
        { "question": "高級", "answer": "こうきゅう", "english_answer": "high class/grade" },
        { "question": "上級", "answer": "じょうきゅう", "english_answer": "advanced level" },
        { "question": "中級", "answer": "ちゅうきゅう", "english_answer": "intermediate level" },
        { "question": "残業", "answer": "ざんぎょう", "english_answer": "overtime work" },
        { "question": "残る", "answer": "のこる", "english_answer": "remain" },
        { "question": "残り", "answer": "のこり", "english_answer": "remainder" },
        { "question": "残す", "answer": "のこす", "english_answer": "leave, leave behind" },
        { "question": "大型", "answer": "おおがた", "english_answer": "large, jumbo" },
        { "question": "新型", "answer": "しんがた", "english_answer": "new-model" },
        { "question": "小型", "answer": "こがた", "english_answer": "small-sized" },
        { "question": "消費税", "answer": "しょうひぜい", "english_answer": "consumption tax" },
        { "question": "税金", "answer": "ぜいきん", "english_answer": "tax" },
        { "question": "込む", "answer": "こむ", "english_answer": "congest/crowd" },
        { "question": "振り込む", "answer": "ふりこむ", "english_answer": "transfer money to a person's account" },
        { "question": "税込", "answer": "ぜいこみ", "english_answer": "tax included" },
        { "question": "価格", "answer": "かかく", "english_answer": "price" },
        { "question": "定価", "answer": "ていか", "english_answer": "fixed price" },
        { "question": "合格", "answer": "ごうかく", "english_answer": "pass an exam" },
        { "question": "格安", "answer": "かくやす", "english_answer": "bargain" }
    ],
    "N3D25KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "申し込む", "answer": "もうしこむ", "english_answer": "apply" },
        { "question": "申告", "answer": "しんこく", "english_answer": "declaration" },
        { "question": "申す", "answer": "もうす", "english_answer": "say (humble form)" },
        { "question": "申込書", "answer": "もうしこみしょ", "english_answer": "application form" },
        { "question": "申請", "answer": "しんせい", "english_answer": "application" },
        { "question": "申し上げる", "answer": "もうしあげる", "english_answer": "say (very humble form)" },
        { "question": "記入", "answer": "きにゅう", "english_answer": "entry" },
        { "question": "記号", "answer": "きごう", "english_answer": "sign, symbol" },
        { "question": "日記", "answer": "にっき", "english_answer": "diary, journal" },
        { "question": "記事", "answer": "きじ", "english_answer": "article" },
        { "question": "例", "answer": "れい", "english_answer": "example" },
        { "question": "例えば", "answer": "たとえば", "english_answer": "for example" },
        { "question": "年齢", "answer": "ねんれい", "english_answer": "age" },
        { "question": "高齢", "answer": "こうれい", "english_answer": "old age" },
        { "question": "～歳", "answer": "さい", "english_answer": "years old" },
        { "question": "二十歳", "answer": "はたち", "english_answer": "20 years old" },
        { "question": "性別", "answer": "せいべつ", "english_answer": "sex, gender" },
        { "question": "女性", "answer": "じょせい", "english_answer": "woman" },
        { "question": "性格", "answer": "せいかく", "english_answer": "personality" },
        { "question": "男性", "answer": "だんせい", "english_answer": "man" },
        { "question": "連休", "answer": "れんきゅう", "english_answer": "holiday" },
        { "question": "連れて行く", "answer": "つれていく", "english_answer": "take someone to" },
        { "question": "連れて来る", "answer": "つれてくる", "english_answer": "bring someone to" },
        { "question": "連絡", "answer": "れんらく", "english_answer": "contact" }
    ],
    "N3D26KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "届ける", "answer": "とどける", "english_answer": "deliver" },
        { "question": "届く", "answer": "とどく", "english_answer": "arrive (mail)" },
        { "question": "自宅", "answer": "じたく", "english_answer": "one's house/home" },
        { "question": "宅配", "answer": "たくはい", "english_answer": "deliver to someone's house" },
        { "question": "お宅", "answer": "おたく", "english_answer": "house/home (respectful form)" },
        { "question": "配達", "answer": "はいたつ", "english_answer": "delivery" },
        { "question": "心配", "answer": "しんぱい", "english_answer": "anxiety/worry" },
        { "question": "配送料", "answer": "はいそうりょう", "english_answer": "shipping charge" },
        { "question": "配る", "answer": "くばる", "english_answer": "distribute" },
        { "question": "希望", "answer": "きぼう", "english_answer": "hope" },
        { "question": "失望", "answer": "しつぼう", "english_answer": "despair" },
        { "question": "望む", "answer": "のぞむ", "english_answer": "want, hope for" },
        { "question": "入荷", "answer": "にゅうか", "english_answer": "receipt (of goods)" },
        { "question": "荷物", "answer": "にもつ", "english_answer": "luggage" },
        { "question": "出荷", "answer": "しゅっか", "english_answer": "shipment" },
        { "question": "手荷物", "answer": "てにもつ", "english_answer": "hand luggage" },
        { "question": "交換", "answer": "こうかん", "english_answer": "exchange" },
        { "question": "乗り換え", "answer": "のりかえ", "english_answer": "changing trains" },
        { "question": "代金引換", "answer": "だいきんひきかえ", "english_answer": "cash on delivery" },
        { "question": "金額", "answer": "きんがく", "english_answer": "amount/sum (of money)" },
        { "question": "半額", "answer": "はんがく", "english_answer": "half price" }
    ],
    "N3D27KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "不在", "answer": "ふざい", "english_answer": "absence" },
        { "question": "現在", "answer": "げんざい", "english_answer": "present (time)" },
        { "question": "取る", "answer": "とる", "english_answer": "take" },
        { "question": "受け取る", "answer": "うけとる", "english_answer": "receive, take" },
        { "question": "受取人", "answer": "うけとりにん", "english_answer": "recipient" },
        { "question": "預金", "answer": "よきん", "english_answer": "money deposit" },
        { "question": "預ける", "answer": "あずける", "english_answer": "entrust" },
        { "question": "衣類", "answer": "いるい", "english_answer": "clothing" },
        { "question": "衣服", "answer": "いふく", "english_answer": "clothes" },
        { "question": "参加", "answer": "さんか", "english_answer": "participate" },
        { "question": "参る", "answer": "まいる", "english_answer": "go/come (humble form)" },
        { "question": "参考書", "answer": "さんこうしょ", "english_answer": "reference book" },
        { "question": "上達", "answer": "じょうたつ", "english_answer": "make progress" },
        { "question": "友達", "answer": "ともだち", "english_answer": "friend" },
        { "question": "速達", "answer": "そくたつ", "english_answer": "special delivery" },
        { "question": "通勤", "answer": "つうきん", "english_answer": "commuting to work" },
        { "question": "勤める", "answer": "つとめる", "english_answer": "work, be employed" },
        { "question": "携帯（電話）", "answer": "けいたい（でんわ）", "english_answer": "cell phone, mobile phone" },
        { "question": "帯", "answer": "おび", "english_answer": "belt, sash" },
        { "question": "時間帯", "answer": "じかんたい", "english_answer": "time zone, time slot" }
    ],
    "N3D28KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "細い", "answer": "ほそい", "english_answer": "fine, thin" },
        { "question": "細かい", "answer": "こまかい", "english_answer": "fine, small" },
        { "question": "戸", "answer": "と", "english_answer": "door" },
        { "question": "戸だな", "answer": "とだな", "english_answer": "closet, cupboard" },
        { "question": "雨戸", "answer": "あまど", "english_answer": "sliding storm door" },
        { "question": "びわ湖", "answer": "びわこ", "english_answer": "Lake Biwa" },
        { "question": "湖", "answer": "みずうみ", "english_answer": "lake" },
        { "question": "風船", "answer": "ふうせん", "english_answer": "balloon" },
        { "question": "船", "answer": "ふね", "english_answer": "boat, ship" },
        { "question": "船長", "answer": "せんちょう", "english_answer": "captain" },
        { "question": "船便", "answer": "ふなびん", "english_answer": "surface/sea mail" },
        { "question": "角度", "answer": "かくど", "english_answer": "angle" },
        { "question": "四角い", "answer": "しかくい", "english_answer": "square" },
        { "question": "三角形", "answer": "さんかくけい", "english_answer": "triangle" },
        { "question": "角", "answer": "かど", "english_answer": "corner" },
        { "question": "夫妻", "answer": "ふさい", "english_answer": "husband and wife" },
        { "question": "夫婦", "answer": "ふうふ", "english_answer": "married couple" },
        { "question": "夫", "answer": "おっと", "english_answer": "husband" },
        { "question": "苦労", "answer": "くろう", "english_answer": "hardship" },
        { "question": "苦い", "answer": "にがい", "english_answer": "bitter" },
        { "question": "苦しい", "answer": "くるしい", "english_answer": "distressful, trying" },
        { "question": "苦手", "answer": "にがて", "english_answer": "weak point" }
    ],
    "N3D29KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "お礼", "answer": "おれい", "english_answer": "thanks" },
        { "question": "伺う", "answer": "うかがう", "english_answer": "visit, ask (humble form)" },
        { "question": "遅刻", "answer": "ちこく", "english_answer": "tardiness" },
        { "question": "遅い", "answer": "おそい", "english_answer": "slow" },
        { "question": "遅れる", "answer": "おくれる", "english_answer": "be late" },
        { "question": "失礼", "answer": "しつれい", "english_answer": "rudeness" },
        { "question": "失敗", "answer": "しっぱい", "english_answer": "failure, mistake" },
        { "question": "失礼する", "answer": "しつれいする", "english_answer": "be excused" },
        { "question": "汗", "answer": "あせ", "english_answer": "perspiration, sweat" },
        { "question": "汗を掻く", "answer": "あせをかく", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "残念", "answer": "ざんねん", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "記念", "answer": "きねん", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "涙", "answer": "なみだ", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "涙を流す", "answer": "なみだをながす", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "笑う", "answer": "わらう", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "笑顔", "answer": "えがお", "english_answer": "" },
        { "question": "笑い", "answer": "わらい", "english_answer": "" }
    ],
    "N3D30KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "", "answer": "", "english_answer": "" },
    ],
    "N3D31KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "", "answer": "", "english_answer": "" },
    ],
    "N3D32KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "", "answer": "", "english_answer": "" },
    ],
    "N3D33KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "", "answer": "", "english_answer": "" },
    ],
    "N3D34KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "", "answer": "", "english_answer": "" },
    ],
    "N3D35KQuiz" : [
        { "question": "", "answer": "", "english_answer": "" },
    ]
}
